soldier- readme

The generic enemy, ally, and player4 palettes are already built into the animation packages, 
but if you want to change them or need to re-insert them because you altered the animation, 
there are alternate-palette versions of frame000.png in the lance frames' folder which can
be imported into BwdYeti's FERecolor app.

The map sprites have a different palette from the vanilla one, but just uncheck "insert palette" 
while inserting them in GBAGE and it will insert with the vanilla palette intact.

Enjoy! —Alusq